GERALDINE HEWITT

765 Main Avenue, San Francisco, CA 20194 g.hewin@inyemail.com {736} 593-1039

Enthusiastic and hardworking front desk medical receptionist with 1+ years of experience providing outstanding customer service in a fast-paced ophthalmology clinic. Excellent verbal and written communicator with outstanding collaborative skills, Strong knowledge of appointment booking systems and medical administration protocols and procedures.

EDUCATION

ASSOCIATE OF SCIENCE IN HEALTHCARE ADMINISTRATION

University of San Francisco, San Francisco, CA September 2017-June 2019

KEY SKILLS

- ♦ Customer service
- · Billing and invoicing
- Microsoft Office Suite
- ♦ Appointment management
- · Excellent telephone etiquette
- · Productivity and efficiency
- Teamwork

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FRONT DESK MEDICAL RECEPTIONIST

Glaucoma Associates of Northern California, San Francisco, CA July 2019- Present

- Greet patients warmly upon entry to the facility and direct them lo ihe correct location, achieving a consistent 5-star service rating throughout employment
- Process appointment bookings and cancellations with 100% accuracy using the department's online scheduling system
- Assist the senior administrators with billing and invoice generation
- Redirect incoming email and mail correspondence to the correct practitioner via the internal communications network

CALL CENTER REPRESENTATIVE

Alpine Home Air Products, San Francisco, CA September 2015-July 2019

- Processed up to 90 inbound calls per day and facilitated customer queries

 Following proper telephone etiquette
- Kept updated and accurate records on clients' project requirements to pass to specialists
- Followed a strict service script and protocol to ensure consistent, effective assistance, achieving 98% positive feedback from clients
- Worked collaboratively with colleagues to determine the most suitable products and services for each inquiry